The Project Panel is where you store
プロジェクトパネルは
all of the assets that make up your game.
ゲームを構成するすべてのアセットを格納する場所です。
Anything you create with the panel,
パネルを使用して作成するものの全て、
and any asset you import, will be kept here.
インポートしたアセットの全ては、ここに保管されます。
You can create Unity-specific assets by clicking the
Unity 特有のアセットを作成するには
create button at the top.
最上部にある Create ボタンをクリックします。
Or import assets created in an external application.
あるいは、外部アプリケーションにより作成されたアセットをインポートします。
You can import by right clicking,
インポートするには右クリックするか、
by using the top menu
トップメニューを使用するか、
or simply by adding files to the assets folder in your operating system
あるいは単に OS でのAssets フォルダにファイルを追加するか、
or by saving from another application.
別のアプリケーションのファイルをここに保存します。
The project panel is a mirror of your assets folder.
プロジェクトパネルは Assets フォルダとまったく同じ内容になります。
And when viewing the assets folder in your operating system
そして OS 上の Assets フォルダを表示すると
you'll notice that meta files are created for
プロジェクトで配置されている全てのアセットには
every asset that's placed in to the project.
メタファイルが作成されていることに気付きます。
Note that once the asset is in you should always use
アセットが一回置かれた後は、これを移動したり編集するときは
the project panel to move it around or edit it
OS 上で編集するのではなく
rather than using your operating system
つねにプロジェクトパネルを使用すべきです。
as this can break lines in the library of your project.
そうしなければプロジェクトライブラリのリンクが壊れることがあります。
The project panel has two styles of view,
プロジェクトパネルには二種類のビューがあり、
one and two column.
1 列表示と 2 列表示です。
These can be switched by clicking the context menu
これらは右上にあるコンテキストメニューをクリックして
button in the top right.
切り替えることが出来ます。
One column view lets you see assets in a simple hierarchy as shown here.
1 列表示のビューによりアセットを次のような単純な階層表示ができます。
Two column view gives you more flexibility
2 列表示のビューはより柔軟性があり、
and more options to work with assets.
アセットで作業するうえでのオプションがあります。
You can select, move and duplicate assets in the project.
プロジェクト上でアセットを選択、移動、および複製することが出来ます。
Create and organise in to folders.
さらにフォルダの中で作成、整理が出来ます。
As well as label assets and search for them.
さらにアセットにラベルづけをして検索できます。
Assets can also be previewed in a thumbnail form
アセットをサムネイルでプレビュー表示するには
by dragging the slider at the bottom,
最下部にあるスライダをドラッグして
with hierarchies then being shown with a right-arrow
階層は次のような右矢印アイコンで表示され
that can be used to expand or collapse them.
このアイコンで展開または折りたたみをすることが出来ます。
Assets can also be searched for
アセットの検索および
and sorted by their name,
名前、型、ラベルでの
their type, a label
並び替えをしたり
or by a favourite grouping.
好きにグルーピングできます。
To create favourites you could perform a search
お気に入りを作成するには、検索実行をして
and then click the star button in the top right
右上のスターボタンをクリックして
and give your new group a name.
新規のグループに名前をつけます。
You can even search the assets store from the project browser.
プロジェクトブラウザからアセットストアの検索さえも出来ます。
By typing in the standard search field
操作としては標準の検索フィールドに入力して
and switching from assets to asset store.
Assets から Asset Store に切り替えます。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)